<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 City POI Guam Points for: Guam in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>City based geocoding reference layer.</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>144.66226</westbc><eastbc>144.9083</eastbc><northbc>13.56562</northbc><southbc>13.26437</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>Guam</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>Boundaries for cartographic features may be generalized. Generalisation refers to the process of reusing existing links when cartography and administrative boundaries are created. If existing geometry is within the generalization guidelines below, then the feature is added to the existing links instead of creating additional geometry. Roads and ferries cannot share geometry with railways, runways, country boundaries, or any water links. Additionally, Building/Landmark polygons which require sufficient detail to make the building recognisable, can never share geometry with navigable links. All other cartography may share geometry based on the generalisation rules. For example, a road link or railroad link may also have a feature of state park or hospital. Cartography and administrative boundary features in Detailed City areas can be generalised up to 25 metres/82 feet (except built-up areas) and 100 metres/328 feet for built-up areas Cartography and administrative boundary features in Inter-Town areas can be  eneralised up to 250 metres/820 feet (except built-up areas) 100 metres/328 feet for built-up areas.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><spdoinfo><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf><sdtsterm><sdtstype>Entity Point</sdtstype><ptvctcnt>19</ptvctcnt></sdtsterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><spref><horizsys><geograph><latres>0.00001</latres><longres>0.00001</longres><geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit></geograph><geodetic><horizdn>D_WGS_1984</horizdn><ellips>WGS_1984</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis><denflat>298.257224</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>CityPOI_Guam</enttypl><enttypd>City based geocoding reference layer.</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape - ESRI geometry object.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>POI_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>POI ID - Unique ID for the POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all POI_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CAT_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Category ID - The Category ID defines the type of POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4444</edomv><edomvd>Named Place</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ISO_COUNTRY_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>ISO Country Code - A three-letter country code as defined by the International Organization for Standardization. The ISO Country Code indicates in which country the feature is located. Different layers describe different features. ISO Country Code attribution is applied to Navigable Links, Administrative Hierarchies, and POIs in various layers.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>GUM</edomv><edomvd>GUAM</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LANGUAGE_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>Language Code - The language associated with the feature name. The Language Code, in conjunction with Prefix, Feature Name, Street Type, and Suffix, can be used in destination selection, route guidance, and map display.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>ENG</edomv><edomvd>ENGLISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>POI_NAME</attrlabl><attrdef>Poi Name - The POI Name is the Preferred, Official Name of the POI. POI Names can be used for destination selection and map display for languages supported by HERE.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all POI_NAME values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NAMED_PLACE_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Named Place ID - The Named Place ID is the ID of the Administrative Area or Zone associated with the City POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all NAMED_PLACE_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NAMED_PLACE_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Named Place Type - The Named Place Type indicates what ID the Named Place ID refers to.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>A</edomv><edomvd>Admin</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>VANITY_CITY_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Vanity City ID - The Vanity City ID is the Admin Place ID representing the Vanity City of the POI. Key into the Admin table.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all VANITY_CITY_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Display ID - The Display ID is a value which can be used for map display to render POIs in a logical manner.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all DISPLAY_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>STREET_ADDRESS_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Address ID - Unique identifier for a named, addressed navigable link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all STREET_ADDRESS_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LINK_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Link ID - Unique identifier for the Link to which the Street Address relates. Link ID is used to identify each link in the database.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LINK_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIDE</attrlabl><attrdef>Side - The Side of the link where the POI is located.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>NOT APPLICABLE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>POPULATION</attrlabl><attrdef>Population - The Population of a city represented by a Named Place POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all POPULATION values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ADMIN_PLACE_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Admin Place ID - The Admin Place ID is a unique identifier of the lowest administrative level in the hierarchy.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ADMIN_PLACE_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>POSTAL_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>Postal Code - Provides the Postal Code area in which the POI is located.While this feature can be used for destination selection this is usually not recommended, except in the case of refined address resolution. For example, when the same address exists twice within a city, a postal code selection may narrow down which address is preferred.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all POSTAL_CODE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CAPITAL_COUNTRY</attrlabl><attrdef>Capital Country - Capital Country indicates if a City POI is the capital of the country.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CAPITAL_COUNTRY values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CAPITAL_ORDER1</attrlabl><attrdef>Capital Order 1 - Captial Order1 indicates if a City POI is the capital of the Order1 area.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CAPITAL_ORDER1 values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CAPITAL_ORDER2</attrlabl><attrdef>Capital Order 2 - Captial Order2 indicates if a City POI is the capital of the Order2 area.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CAPITAL_ORDER2 values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CAPITAL_ORDER8</attrlabl><attrdef>Capital Orde r8 - Captial Order8 indicates if a City POI is the capital of the Order8 area.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CAPITAL_ORDER8 values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CLAIMED_BY</attrlabl><attrdef>Claimed By - Claimed By indicates which country claims a Named Place POI in a disputed area. It is only coded for areas that are under dispute.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CLAIMED_BY values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CONTROLLED_BY</attrlabl><attrdef>Controlled By - The Controlled By attribute is used to indicate which country is in control of the area in which the Named Place POI is located. It is only coded in areas that are under dispute.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CONTROLLED_BY values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LOCATION_SCORE</attrlabl><attrdef>Location Score - Location Score provides a percentage value indicating the confidence of location accuracy. The Location Score ranges in value from 0 - 100.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LOCATION_SCORE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PLACE_SCORE</attrlabl><attrdef>Place Score - Place Score provides a percentage value indicating the completeness of POI attribution. The Place Score ranges in value from 0 - 100.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all PLACE_SCORE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CALCULATED_LEVEL</attrlabl><attrdef>Calculated Level - Calculated Level indicates the overall level of completion and accuracy of a POI. The Calculated Level ranges from 1-4.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_LAT</attrlabl><attrdef>Display Latitude - The Display Latitude is the latitude of the display position of the POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all DISPLAY_LAT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_LON</attrlabl><attrdef>Display Longitude - The Display Longitude is the longitude of the display position of the POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all DISPLAY_LON values</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>