<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 Condition Transport Table for: North America in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>All attributes related to the Transport conditions are published in the table ConditionTransport. This involves the attributes for the following condition types: * Condition Type = 23 (Transport Access Restriction) * Condition Type = 25 (Transport Special Speed Situation) * Condition Type = 26 (Transport Restricted Driving Manoeuvre) * Condition Type = 27 (Transport Preferred Route)</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-180</westbc><eastbc>180</eastbc><northbc>83.11062</northbc><southbc>-14.5487</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey><themekey>preferred transport routes</themekey><themekey>special speed situations</themekey><themekey>transport restrictions</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>American Samoa</placekey><placekey>Guam and the Northern Mariana Islands</placekey><placekey>North America</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>There is no positional accuracy directly associated with non-geometric tables.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>ConditionTransport</enttypl><enttypd>All attributes related to the Transport conditions are published in the table ConditionTransport. This involves the attributes for the following condition types: * Condition Type = 23 (Transport Access Restriction) * Condition Type = 25 (Transport Special Speed Situation) * Condition Type = 26 (Transport Restricted Driving Manoeuvre) * Condition Type = 27 (Transport Preferred Route)</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CONDITION_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Condition ID - Condition ID publishes the HERE Condition ID that is represented by the Turn.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CONDITION_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>WEIGHT_RESTRICTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Weight Restriction - Weight Restriction specifies the occurrence of a (total) weight restriction on a link or lane limiting access to vehicles exceeding a specific (total) weight. Weight Restriction can be used to restrict access of vehicles to specific links or lanes based on the vehicle’s weight.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all WEIGHT_RESTRICTION values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>HEIGHT_RESTRICTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Height Restriction - Height Restriction specifies the occurrence of a height restriction on a link or lane limiting access to vehicles exceeding a specific height. Height Restriction can be used to restrict access of vehicles to specific links or lanes based on the vehicle’s height.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all HEIGHT_RESTRICTION values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LENGTH_RESTRICTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Length Restriction - The MARC Language Code applicable to the Zone Name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LENGTH_RESTRICTION values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>WIDTH_RESTRICTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Width Restriction - Width Restriction specifies the occurrence of a width restriction on a link or lane limiting access to vehicles exceeding a specific width. Width Restriction can be used to restrict access of vehicles to specific links or lanes based on the vehicle’s width.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all WIDTH_RESTRICTION values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>WEIGHT_PER_AXLE_RESTRICTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Weight Per Axle Restriction - Weight per Axle Restriction specifies the occurrence of a weight per axle restriction on a link or lane limiting access to trucks where the weight per axle is exceeding a specific weight. Weight per Axle Restriction can be used to restrict access of trucks to specific links or lanes based on the truck’s weight per axle.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all WEIGHT_PER_AXLE_RESTRICTION values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NUMBER_OF_AXLES</attrlabl><attrdef>Number Of Axles - Number of Axles is used to model signs specifying the number of axles that are restricted.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>Two or more Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>Three or more Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>Four or more Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>Five or more Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>Six or more Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>Single Axle</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>Tandem Axle</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>Triple Axle</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>11</edomv><edomvd>Two Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>12</edomv><edomvd>Three Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>13</edomv><edomvd>Four Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>14</edomv><edomvd>Five Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>15</edomv><edomvd>Six Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>16</edomv><edomvd>Seven Axles</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>KPRA_LENGTH</attrlabl><attrdef>KPRA Length - KPRA is used to model signs specifying the “Kingpin to Rear Axle” length. These signs are only published in North America.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all KPRA_LENGTH values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>HAZARDOUS_MATERIAL_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Hazardous Material Type - Hazardous Material Type is a sub-attribute to the Transport Access Restriction or Transport Restricted Driving Manoeuvre condition and defines the type of hazardous good(s) for which a specific link or lane is closed. Hazardous Material Type can be used to detail the Transport Access Restriction to vehicles with specific goods.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>EXPLOSIVES</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>GAS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>FLAMMABLE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>FLAMMABLE SOLID/COMBUSTIBLE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>ORGANIC</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>POISON</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>RADIOACTIVE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>CORROSIVE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>9</edomv><edomvd>OTHER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>20</edomv><edomvd>ANY HAZARDOUS MATERIAL</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>21</edomv><edomvd>POISONOUS INHALATION HAZARD (PIH)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>HAZMAT_PERMIT_REQUIRED</attrlabl><attrdef>Hazmat Permit Required - HazMat Permit Required applies in areas where the driver is required to have a HAZMAT Permit document to legally drive on the road with hazardous cargo. This requirement is typically not posted.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>9</edomv><edomvd>Any Hazardous Material Permit</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DIRECTION_CLOSURE</attrlabl><attrdef>Direction Closure - Direction Closure (38) is an attribute to the Transport Access Restriction condition and defines the direction of the link or lane closed for vehicles with specific legal or physical restrictions. Direction Closure can be used to close links or lanes in the specified direction, for trucks with a specific usage or vehicles with specific loads. Direction Closure is only used to close links or lanes for a specific direction, it is not used to ‘open’ links in a specific direction.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>CLOSED IN BOTH DIRECTIONS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>CLOSED IN POSITIVE DIRECTION</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>CLOSED IN NEGATIVE DIRECTION</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRAILER_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Trailer Type - Trailer Type specifies the occurrence of a restriction on a link or lane related to trucks with a specified number of trailers. Trailer Type can be used to restrict access of vehicles to specific links or lanes based on the number of trailers attached to a truck.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>TRUCK WITH ONE OR MORE TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>TRUCK WITH TWO OR MORE TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>TRUCK WITH THREE OR MORE TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>SEMI OR TRACTOR WITH 1 OR MORE TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>TRUCK WITH NO TRAILER(S)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>TRUCK WITH ONE TRAILER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>TRUCK WITH TWO TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>10</edomv><edomvd>STRAIGHT TRUCK WITH ONE OR MORE TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>13</edomv><edomvd>STRAIGHT TRUCK WITH OR WITHOUT TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>14</edomv><edomvd>STRAIGHT TRUCK WITH NO TRAILER(S)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>19</edomv><edomvd>SEMI-TRUCK WITH ONE OR MORE TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>20</edomv><edomvd>SEMI-TRUCK WITH TWO OR MORE TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>22</edomv><edomvd>SEMI-TRUCK WITH OR WITHOUT TRAILERS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PHYSICAL_STRUCTURE_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Physical Structure Type - Physical Structure Type is used to specify if a Transport Access Restriction is caused by a Bridge (Overpass) or Tunnel (Underpass) or any other type of structure like cables, pipelines etc. Physical Structure Type can be used to refine the guidance in case of physical restrictions present on a road.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>BRIDGE (OVERPASS)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>TUNNEL (UNDERPASS)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>ARCH BRIDGE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>ARCH TUNNEL</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>OTHER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRANSPORT_SPEED_LIMIT</attrlabl><attrdef>Transport Speed Limit - The Transport Speed Limit is a Transport Special Speed Situation condition attribute and indicates the speed limit applicable to transportation vehicles. The Transport Speed Limit can be used to alert the truck driver for truck-specific speed limits applicable to the road.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all TRANSPORT_SPEED_LIMIT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRANSPORT_SPEED_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Transport Speed Type - The Transport Speed Type condition attribute indicates the type of transport speed limit. This includes special speed limits for trucks with hazardous goods, weather dependent transport speed limits etc. The Transport Speed Type can be used to give specific speed limit warning messages based on the type of speed limit.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>TRAILER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>WEIGHT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SPEED_LIMIT_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Speed Limit Type - Speed Limit Type indicates if the Transport Speed Limit is Legal or Advisory.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>Legal</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>Advisory</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DIRECTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Direction - Direction is a general condition modifier used for select single-link conditions that indicates the link direction for which a direction-dependent attribute is applicable. Direction is a sub-attribute to direction dependent condition coding. Direction can be used to retrieve the link direction for which the No Overtaking and Protected Overtaking condition applies.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>FROM REFERENCE NODE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>TO REFERENCE NODE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>BOTH DIRECTIONS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>WEIGHT_DEPENDENT</attrlabl><attrdef>Weight Dependent - Weight Dependent is a general condition attribute used for select single-link conditions and provides the weight related to specific Transport conditions. Weight Dependent is used as a sub-attribute to specific restrictions, and is not used to model weight restrictions on roads. Weight Dependent can be used to display the weight together with the transport condition for which a weight dependency exists.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all WEIGHT_DEPENDENT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>WEATHER_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Weather Type - Weather Type provides the weather type related to the Transport Special Speed Situation condition. This sub-attribute indicates the type of weather condition that is affecting the transport speed limit. Weather Type can be used to display the type of weather condition affecting the truckspecific speed limit or to alert the driver for truck-specific speed limits on the road.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PREFERRED_ROUTE_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Preferred Route Type - Preferred Route Type is an attribute of the Transport Preferred Route condition and defines the type of preferred route published. Preferred Route Type can be used to refine the preferred route to specific trucks or trucks with specific goods. This allows for tuning the preferred route options to the qualifications of the applicable truck.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>STAA</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>TD</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>NRHM (NAT'L REPOS NON-RADIOACTV HAZMATS)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>CLASS 1 HAZARDOUS MATERIALS (EXPLOSIVES)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>PIH (POISONOUS INHALATION HAZMATS)</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>RADIOACTIVE MATERIAL</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>GENERAL HAZARDOUS GOODS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>9</edomv><edomvd>LOCAL</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>15</edomv><edomvd>FUNCTIONAL CLASS 1 OVERRIDE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>16</edomv><edomvd>FUNCTIONAL CLASS 2 OVERRIDE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TIME_OVERRIDE</attrlabl><attrdef>Time Override - The Time Override indicates if the Special Speed Limit is only applicable from Dusk to Dawn or Dawn to Dusk.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>DAWN TO DUSK</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>DUSK TO DAWN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>