<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 Condition Driver Alert Table for: North America in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>All attributes related to Driver Alert conditions are stored in the table ConditionDriverAlert. This involves the attributes for the following condition types: * Condition Type = 16 (Traffic Light) * Condition Type = 17 (Traffic Sign) * Condition Type = 18 (Railway Crossing) * Condition Type = 19 (No Overtaking) * Condition Type = 21 (Protected Overtaking)</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-180</westbc><eastbc>180</eastbc><northbc>83.11062</northbc><southbc>-14.5487</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey><themekey>driving condition alerts</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>American Samoa</placekey><placekey>Guam and the Northern Mariana Islands</placekey><placekey>North America</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>There is no positional accuracy directly associated with non-geometric tables.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>ConditionDriverAlert</enttypl><enttypd>All attributes related to Driver Alert conditions are stored in the table ConditionDriverAlert. This involves the attributes for the following condition types: * Condition Type = 16 (Traffic Light) * Condition Type = 17 (Traffic Sign) * Condition Type = 18 (Railway Crossing) * Condition Type = 19 (No Overtaking) * Condition Type = 21 (Protected Overtaking)</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CONDITION_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Condition ID - Condition ID publishes the HERE Condition ID that is represented by the Turn.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CONDITION_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRAFFIC_SIGN_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Traffic Sign Type - The Traffic Sign Type identifies the type of warning sign. The Traffic Sign Type can be used to give specific driver alert messaging using the sign type. Traffic Sign Type can also be used to display the Traffic Sign. Warning signs can be used in optimizing route calculation.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>START OF NO OVERTAKING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>END OF NO OVERTAKING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>PROTECTED OVERTAKING - EXTRA LANE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>PROTECTED OVERTAKING - EXTRA LANE RIGHT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>PROTECTED OVERTAKING - EXTRA LANE LEFT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>LANE MERGING FROM THE RIGHT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>LANE MERGING FROM THE LEFT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>LANE MERGE CENTRE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>9</edomv><edomvd>RAILWAY CROSSING PROTECTED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>10</edomv><edomvd>RAILWAY CROSSING UNPROTECTED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>11</edomv><edomvd>ROAD NARROWS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>12</edomv><edomvd>SHARP CURVE LEFT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>13</edomv><edomvd>SHARP CURVE RIGHT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>14</edomv><edomvd>WINDING ROAD STARTING LEFT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>15</edomv><edomvd>WINDING ROAD STARTING RIGHT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>16</edomv><edomvd>START OF NO OVERTAKING TRUCKS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>17</edomv><edomvd>END OF NO OVERTAKING TRUCKS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>18</edomv><edomvd>STEEP HILL UPWARDS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>19</edomv><edomvd>STEEP HILL DOWNWARDS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>20</edomv><edomvd>STOP SIGN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>21</edomv><edomvd>LATERAL WIND</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>22</edomv><edomvd>GENERAL WARNING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>23</edomv><edomvd>RISK OF GROUNDING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>24</edomv><edomvd>GENERAL CURVE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>25</edomv><edomvd>END OF ALL RESTRICTIONS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>26</edomv><edomvd>GENERAL HILL</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>27</edomv><edomvd>ANIMAL CROSSING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>28</edomv><edomvd>ICY CONDITIONS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>29</edomv><edomvd>SLIPPERY ROAD</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>30</edomv><edomvd>FALLING ROCKS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>31</edomv><edomvd>SCHOOL ZONE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>32</edomv><edomvd>TRAMWAY CROSSING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>33</edomv><edomvd>CONGESTION HAZARD</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>34</edomv><edomvd>ACCIDENT HAZARD</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>36</edomv><edomvd>YIELD TO ONCOMING TRAFFIC</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>41</edomv><edomvd>PEDESTRIAN CROSSING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>42</edomv><edomvd>YIELD</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>53</edomv><edomvd>NO ENGINE BRAKE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>54</edomv><edomvd>END OF NO ENGINE BRAKE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>55</edomv><edomvd>NO IDLING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>56</edomv><edomvd>TRUCK ROLLOVER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>57</edomv><edomvd>LOW GEAR</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>58</edomv><edomvd>END OF LOW GEAR</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>64</edomv><edomvd>NO TURN ON RED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>65</edomv><edomvd>TURN PERMITTED ON RED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRAFFIC_SIGN_VALUE</attrlabl><attrdef>Traffic Sign Value - The Traffic Sign modifier Traffic Sign Value provides values visible on the sign related to specific sign types. Traffic Sign Value can be used to display the traffic signs with the exact restriction or information as provided on the sign.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all TRAFFIC_SIGN_VALUE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>GEN_WARNING_SIGN_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>General Warning Sign Type - The Traffic Sign modifier General Warning Sign Type is used to specify the nature or a general warning sign (Traffic Sign Type = 22). General Warning Sign Type can be used to explicitly indicate the type of warning for a General Warning sign.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>OBJECT OVERHANG</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>RISK OF GROUNDING</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRAFFIC_SIGN_CATEGORY</attrlabl><attrdef>Traffic Sign Category - Traffic Sign Category identifies the main sign category to which the sign belongs to. Traffic Sign Category can be used to give specific informative messaging.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>REGULATORY TRAFFIC SIGN CATEGORY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>SAFETY INFORMATION TRAFFIC SIGN CATEGORY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>WARNING TRAFFIC SIGN CATEGORY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRAFFIC_SIGN_SUBCATEGORY</attrlabl><attrdef>Traffic Sign Subcategory - The Traffic Sign Subcategory is an attribute that identifies the sub-category of TRAFFIC_SIGN_CATEGORY = 1 - Regulatory Sign. Traffic Sign Subcategory can be used to group Traffic Signs related to Priority.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all TRAFFIC_SIGN_SUBCATEGORY values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_DURATION</attrlabl><attrdef>Supplemental Sign Duration - The Traffic Sign attribute Supplemental Sign Duration indicates additional sign shield that are displayed below the Traffic Sign indicating the duration of the warning. Note: Existing Supplemental Sign Duration is extended to allow for multiple Supplemental Sign Duration attributes for one Traffic Sign. A Language Code field is added to the ConditionText layer to explicitly indicate the language in which the Supplemental Sign Duration is published. File Geodatabase only publishes Latin-1 supplemental sign text. The supplemental sign duration can be used for map display or to indicate the duration of the warning in the driver alert messaging.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_DURATION values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_PREWARNING</attrlabl><attrdef>Supplemental Sign Pre-Warning - The Traffic Sign condition attribute Supplemental Sign Pre-Warning indicates additional sign shields that are displayed below the Traffic Sign indicating an upcoming warning or regulation. These signs are only included when no additional Traffic Sign is present at the actual start of the warning or regulation. Note: Existing Supplemental Sign Pre-Warning is extended to allow for multiple Supplemental Sign Pre-Warning modifiers for one Traffic Sign condition. A Language Code field is added to ConditionText layer to explicitly indicate the language in which the Supplemental Sign Duration is published. File Geodatabase only publishes Latin-1 sign text. The supplemental sign pre-warning can be used for map display or to indicate a prewarning for an upcoming warning or regulation in the driver alert messaging.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_PREWARNING values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_VALIDITY_TIME</attrlabl><attrdef>Supplemental Sign Validity Time - The Traffic Sign condition attribute Supplemental Sign Validity Time indicates that an additional sign shields exists, displayed below the Traffic Sign, indicating a specific time(s) at which the Traffic Sign is applicable. Example: No overtaking for Trucks from 8:30 till 18:00 hours. Existing Supplemental Sign Pre-Warning is extended to allow for multiple Supplemental Sign Pre-Warning modifiers for one Traffic Sign condition. A Language Code field is added to ConditionText layer to explicitly indicate the language in which the Supplemental Sign Duration is published. File Geodatabase only publishes Latin-1 supplemental sign text. Supplemental sign text for validity time can be used to display the supplemental traffic sign with information as present on the sign.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_VALIDITY_TIME values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_VEHICLE_TRUCK</attrlabl><attrdef>Sign Vehicle Truck - Sign Vehicle Truck indicates if a supplemental sign applies to trucks.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_VEHICLE_TRUCK values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_VEHICLE_HEAVY_TRUCK</attrlabl><attrdef>Sign Vehicle Heavy Truck - Sign Vehicle Heavy Truck indicates if a supplemental sign applies to heavy trucks.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_VEHICLE_HEAVY_TRUCK values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_VEHICLE_BUS</attrlabl><attrdef>Sign Vehicle Bus - Sign Vehicle Bus indicates if a supplemental sign applies to buses.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_VEHICLE_BUS values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_VEHICLE_AUTO_TRAILER</attrlabl><attrdef>Sign Vehicle Auto Trailer - Sign Vehicle Auto Trailer indicates if a supplemental sign applies to auto trailers.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_VEHICLE_AUTO_TRAILER values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_VEHICLE_MOTORHOME</attrlabl><attrdef>Sign Vehicle Motorhome - Sign Vehicle Motorhome indicates if a supplemental sign applies to motorhomes.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_VEHICLE_MOTORHOME values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGN_VEHICLE_MOTORCYCLE</attrlabl><attrdef>Sign Vehicle Motorcycle - Sign Vehicle Motorcycle indicates if a supplemental sign applies to motorcycles.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all SIGN_VEHICLE_MOTORCYCLE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DIRECTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Direction - Direction is a general condition modifier used for select single-link conditions that indicates the link direction for which a direction-dependent attribute is applicable. Direction is a sub-attribute to direction dependent condition coding. Direction can be used to retrieve the link direction for which the No Overtaking and Protected Overtaking condition applies.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>FROM REFERENCE NODE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>TO REFERENCE NODE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>BOTH DIRECTIONS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIGNAL_SIGN_LOCATION</attrlabl><attrdef>Signal/sign Location - Signal/Sign Location identifies the location of the Traffic Signal at the intersection. Signal/Sign Location can be used to display the location of the Traffic Signal at the intersection.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>RIGHT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>RAILWAY_CROSSING_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Railway Crossing Type - Railway Crossing Type indicates if the Railway Crossing is protected with a barrier or unprotected without barriers. The supplemental sign displaying validity time can be used for map display.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>PROTECTED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>UNPROTECTED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>WEATHER_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Weather Type - Weather Type provides the weather type related to the Transport Special Speed Situation condition. This sub-attribute indicates the type of weather condition that is affecting the transport speed limit. Weather Type can be used to display the type of weather condition affecting the truckspecific speed limit or to alert the driver for truck-specific speed limits on the road.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>IMPORTANCE_IND</attrlabl><attrdef>Importance Indicator - Importance Indicator is a rating, on a scale of 1 to 10, of the importance of a Bridge, Tunnel, Traffic Signal or Stop Sign for Route Guidance.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all IMPORTANCE_IND values</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>