<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 Link Polylines for: North America in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>The Link table is a central table in the File Geodatabase schema: it contains all Navigable Links in the HERE Map Content. Each Navigable Link which is part of the route network is published in the Link table. The Link table serves various use-cases: * It is relevant for the routing network, and publishes most navigable attribute for a navigable link * It is relevant for the map display, and allows for rendering the navigable network in the map * It is relevant for the geocoding, and enables resolution of an input address to a position in the map. The Link table is a spatial layer and has a geometry object. The geometry publishes all coordinate pairs for the Link: Start Node, Intermediate Shape Points and End Node. The geometry is standard two dimensional (X,Y, where Z-coordinate is not published). [On specific request the geometry can be provided as three dimensional, where the Z-coordinate publishes Absolute Height, where available in the HERE Map Content.]</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-177.38286</westbc><eastbc>179.45298</eastbc><northbc>76.42806</northbc><southbc>-14.5471</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>navigable links</themekey><themekey>routing network</themekey><themekey>streets</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>American Samoa</placekey><placekey>Guam and the Northern Mariana Islands</placekey><placekey>North America</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>The positional accuracy of a given street segment depends on the value of the Enhanced Geometry (ENH_GEOM) attribute. Links with Enhanced Geometry = Y conform to accuracy requirements of +/-5 metres for absolute position and +/- 1 metre for relative position. NOTE: With some linear SDC datasets, there can be 5 different representations of linear street geometry, including one base layer plus 4 increasingly generalized layers, to support rapid display at different zoom levels. The process of generalization removes points, and therefore geometric detail, from the dataset in order to reduce dataset size and improve display times. The suffix number at the end of the base layer name indicates how much generalization has been applied - the higher the number, the more generalization. For example, streets3 is more generalized than streets2. The horizontal positional accuracy described here does NOT apply to these generalized layers, but only to the non-generalized base layer, which will not have a suffix number as part of its name, e.g., streets. The minimum length of any street segment, independent of generalization, is 2 meters/7 feet.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><spdoinfo><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf><sdtsterm><sdtstype>String</sdtstype><ptvctcnt>62431864</ptvctcnt></sdtsterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><spref><horizsys><geograph><latres>0.00001</latres><longres>0.00001</longres><geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit></geograph><geodetic><horizdn>D_WGS_1984</horizdn><ellips>WGS_1984</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis><denflat>298.257224</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>Link</enttypl><enttypd>The Link table is a central table in the File Geodatabase schema: it contains all Navigable Links in the HERE Map Content. Each Navigable Link which is part of the route network is published in the Link table. The Link table serves various use-cases: * It is relevant for the routing network, and publishes most navigable attribute for a navigable link * It is relevant for the map display, and allows for rendering the navigable network in the map * It is relevant for the geocoding, and enables resolution of an input address to a position in the map. The Link table is a spatial layer and has a geometry object. The geometry publishes all coordinate pairs for the Link: Start Node, Intermediate Shape Points and End Node. The geometry is standard two dimensional (X,Y, where Z-coordinate is not published). [On specific request the geometry can be provided as three dimensional, where the Z-coordinate publishes Absolute Height, where available in the HERE Map Content.]</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape - ESRI geometry object.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LINK_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Link ID - Unique identifier for the Link to which the Street Address relates. Link ID is used to identify each link in the database.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LINK_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>REF_NODE_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Reference Node ID - The Reference Node ID is the identifier for the Node which bounds the Link on the Reference End (also known as the ‘From Node’).</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all REF_NODE_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NON_REF_NODE_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Non Reference Node ID - The Non Reference Node ID is the identifier for the Node which bounds the Link on the Non Reference End (also known as the ‘To Node’).</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all NON_REF_NODE_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LEFT_ADMIN_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Admin ID - The Left Admin ID defines the lowest level administrative area on the left side of the Link.This provides information in which City or Settlement the Link is located.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LEFT_ADMIN_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>RIGHT_ADMIN_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Admin ID - The Right Admin ID defines the lowest level administrative area on the right side of the Link. This provides information in which City or Settlement the Link is located.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all RIGHT_ADMIN_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LEFT_POSTAL_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Postal Code - The postal code for the left side of the link. A Postal Code represents the code generated by the government to facilitate mail delivery. While this feature can be used for destination  election this is usually not recommended, except in the case of refined address resolution. For example, when the same address exists twice within a city a postal code selection may narrow down which address is preferred.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LEFT_POSTAL_CODE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>RIGHT_POSTAL_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Postal Code - The postal code for the right side of the link. A Postal Code represents the code generated by the government to facilitate mail delivery. While this feature can be used for destination  election this is usually not recommended, except in the case of refined address resolution. For example, when the same address exists twice within a city a postal code selection may narrow down which address is preferred.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all RIGHT_POSTAL_CODE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ACCESS_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Access ID - The Access ID is the Key into the Vehicle Access table, which is used to indicate which Vehicle Types are allowed to use the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ACCESS_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>STATUS_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Status ID - The Status ID is the Key into the STATUS table, which is used to publish various attributes that provide information on the status of the navigable link (e.g., Detailed City, Urban, In Process Data or Transport Verified). See 5.31 Status (Status) section.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all STATUS_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BRIDGE</attrlabl><attrdef>Bridge - Bridge indicates if the Link is a bridge. A bridge is a structure that allows a road, railroad or walkway to pass over another road, railroad, water feature, or valley.This attribute can be used for display or route guidance.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>Not a Bridge</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Bridge</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TUNNEL</attrlabl><attrdef>Tunnel - Tunnel indicates if the Link is a tunnel. A tunnel is a covered passageway through or This attribute can be used for display or route guidance under an obstruction.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Display ID - The Display ID is a value which can be used for map display to render POIs in a logical manner.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all DISPLAY_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>FUNCTIONAL_CLASS</attrlabl><attrdef>Functional Class - Functional Class defines a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveller. Functional Class can be used to determine sets of links that form connected graphs.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>LEVEL 1</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>LEVEL 2</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>LEVEL 3</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>LEVEL 4</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>LEVEL 5</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CONTROLLED_ACCESS</attrlabl><attrdef>Controlled Access - Controlled Access identifies roads with limited entrances and exits that allow uninterrupted high speed traffic flow. These roads constitute the interstate/freeway network in the U.S. and the motorway network in Europe. The Controlled Access attribute can be used for map display, avoidance of freeway/motorway, and route guidance timing.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TRAVEL_DIRECTION</attrlabl><attrdef>Travel Direction - Travel Direction identifies legal travel directions for a navigable link. Travel Direction enables correct route calculation, route guidance, and map display. For example, display of one-way icon.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>B</edomv><edomvd>BOTH DIRECTIONS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>F</edomv><edomvd>FROM REFERENCE NODE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>T</edomv><edomvd>TO REFERENCE NODE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BOAT_FERRY</attrlabl><attrdef>Boat Ferry - A Boat Ferry represents the generalised route of a ferry for passengers or vehicles over water. This attribute can be used for map display.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>RAIL_FERRY</attrlabl><attrdef>Rail Ferry - A Rail Ferry represents the generalised route of a ferry for passenger vehicles via rail. This attribute can be used for map display.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>MULTI_DIGITIZED</attrlabl><attrdef>Multi-Digitized - The Multiply Digitised attribute identifies links that are digitised with one line per direction of traffic instead of one line per road and using the rules listed below. For wide roads a link is digitised for each direction of traffic (instead of for each road) in order to improve map matching of the car to the road map. The Multiply Digitised attribute identifies these opposing lanes of traffic when it is reasonable to represent them as a single line on displays and printed maps. When route guidance calls for a u-turn involving a multi-digitised road, the guidance  iven should be “make a u-turn at intersection” and not “make a left turn”, followed by “make a left turn.”.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DIVIDER</attrlabl><attrdef>Divider - This attribute identifies the presence of a physical traffic blocking divider.Divider coding enables a system to prevent left turns (in right-side driving countries), right turns (in left-side driving countries), and U-turns at divided intersections and in the middle of divided roads. See diagrams in Specification section below.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>REF NODE AND LINK</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>A</edomv><edomvd>BOTH NODES AND LINK</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>L</edomv><edomvd>LINK ONLY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>NO DIVIDER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>NREF NODE AND LINK</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DIVIDER_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Divider Type - Divider Type indicates if a divider is a Legal or Phsyical divider. In combination with the Divider attribute, enables a system to prevent left turns (in rightside driving countries), right turns (in left side driving countries), and U-turns at divided intersections and in the middle of divided roads. Divider Type identifies physically passable dividers for emergency vehicle routing applications. A physical divider identifies a physical barrier that cannot be traversed.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>L</edomv><edomvd>LEGAL DIVIDER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>P</edomv><edomvd>PHYSICAL DIVIDER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>FRONTAGE</attrlabl><attrdef>Frontage - Frontage Roads (aka Service Roads) are local roads that run parallel to and usually contain the name(s) and addresses of a road with a higher traffic flow. When it is necessary to be guided along the Frontage, the flag enables navigation  systems to provide an appropriate message, for example, “take the Frontage Road.” This attribute enables better route guidance, if this attribute is not taken into consideration, a system might say “you are approaching an intersection of many Main Streets. Take the one in the middle.” The Frontage flag indicates that although the name of the road is the same, the functionality is different. In this way, the strange explications can be avoided.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PAVED</attrlabl><attrdef>Paved - Describes roads that are made of materials which create a solid surface. Paved is primarily used for cartographic representation (map display). This attribute could also affect routing algorithms by assigning higher penalties to unpaved roads.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>RAMP</attrlabl><attrdef>Ramp - Ramps are connectors that provide access between roads that do not cross at grade. This attribute allows explication of manoeuvres involving ramps (e.g. “Take the ramp”). This attribute can also be used for display at different zoom levels or different colors and for route guidance when determining if sign text should be used.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PRIVATE</attrlabl><attrdef>Private - Identifies roads not maintained by an organization responsible for maintenance of public roads. Private allows for unique cartographic representation of roads that restrict public use. Private allows for unique cartographic representation of roads that restrict public use. This attribute could also affect routing algorithms by assigning higher penalties to unpaved roads.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TOLLWAY</attrlabl><attrdef>Tollway - This attribute identifies a link for which a fee must be paid to use the road. Tollway identifies roads that require payments for traversal. This attribute’s intended uses are display and map publishing purposes. This attribute used in conjunction with the Toll Structure condition may be used for toll avoidance routing.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>POI_ACCESS</attrlabl><attrdef>POI Access - POI Access (roads) connect Points of Interest (POIs) to the road network. These roads provide the only means of entrance or exit from a POI to a public road. POI Access attribute allows an entrance to be identified by the POI name for route guidance. For example, the entrance road to a golf course may be explicated as “Turn right at the golf course entrance.”.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>INTERSECTION_CATEGORY</attrlabl><attrdef>Intersection Catetory - Intersection Category defines the type of intersection. It identifies links that are part of or associated with road intersections. These include links created when multiply digitised roads are intersected or when the centrelines of intersecting roads do not meet at a single node. Turn lanes, traffic islands, u-turn lanes, and ramps are also included in the intersection definition. Intersection coding can be used for explication and display. The flags indicate whether a driver will perceive a situation as one or multiple intersections. These flags imply that the situation may require different explication that what is implied by the geometry.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>Intersection Internal</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>Manoeuvre Link</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>Indescribable</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>Roundabout</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>Undefined Traffic Internal</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>Special Traffic Figure</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SPEED_CATEGORY</attrlabl><attrdef>Speed Category - Speed Category classifies the general speed trend of a road based on posted or legal speed and is provided to enhance route calculation and the timing of route guidance. Speed Category values represent the combination of several factors besides legal speed limit (e.g., physical restrictions or access characteristics). Therefore Speed Category values can differ from Speed Limit values, which represent the legal speed limit only. Speed Category may be used to estimate link traversal times, to prioritise link selection during route calculation, and to calculate timing of the route guidance.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>&gt; 130 KPH / &gt; 80 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>101-130 KPH / 65-80 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>91-100 KPH / 55-64 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>71-90 KPH / 41-54 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>51-70 KPH / 31-40 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>31-50 KPH / 21-30 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>11-30 KPH / 6-20 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>&lt; 11 KPH / &lt; 6 MPH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LANE_CATEGORY</attrlabl><attrdef>Lane Category - Lane Category classifies a road based on the number of lanes in each direction. Lane Category can be used for cartographic representation of road widths on printed maps, as well as traffic management and display applications. Lane Category may also be used for route guidance timing.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>ONE LANE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>TWO OR THREE LANES</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>FOUR OR MORE LANES</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>COVERAGE_INDICATOR</attrlabl><attrdef>Coverage Indicator - Coverage Indicator is an attribute to a navigable or non-navigable link that indicates a product level that corresponds to the inclusion of database features. It also indicates verification and completeness for a particular feature in the database.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>B8</edomv><edomvd>BASE - SEARCH AND  DISPLAY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>E7</edomv><edomvd>ENTRY MAP</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>I1</edomv><edomvd>URBAN ROUTING / POINT2POINT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>I2</edomv><edomvd>SEARCH AND DISPLAY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>I3</edomv><edomvd>DISPLAY ONLY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N0</edomv><edomvd>PRIME</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N1</edomv><edomvd>COMPLETE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N4</edomv><edomvd>CITY-TO-CITY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CONFIDENCE_LEVEL_RATING</attrlabl><attrdef>Confidence Level Rating - As of the Q3, 2016 product release, data for this attribute is no longer published.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CONFIDENCE_LEVEL_RATING values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>FROM_REF_NUM_LANES</attrlabl><attrdef>From Reference Number of Langes - This attribute indicates the number of lanes in the positive Link direction (From Reference Node).</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all FROM_REF_NUM_LANES values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TO_REF_NUM_LANES</attrlabl><attrdef>To Reference Number of Lanes - This attribute indicates the number of lanes in the negative Link direction (Towards Reference Node).</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all TO_REF_NUM_LANES values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PHYSICAL_NUM_LANES</attrlabl><attrdef>PHYSICAL NUM LANES - This attribute defines the actual number of lanes physically present on the link. The attribute is introduced for reversible road elements initially, but allows for adoption at non-reversible road elements in the future. Note: Reversible lanes are counted as one lane. Physical Number of Lanes can be used to correctly render the road layout, in combination with lane marking, for reversible links.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all PHYSICAL_NUM_LANES values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>FROM_REF_SPEED_LIMIT</attrlabl><attrdef>From  Referenc Speed  Limit - From/To Speed Limit is the posted or legal speed limit in each travel direction on a road. Speed Limit may be used to estimate link traversal times, to prioritise link selection during route calculation, to calculate timing of the route guidance, and for display purposes.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all FROM_REF_SPEED_LIMIT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TO_REF_SPEED_LIMIT</attrlabl><attrdef>To Reference Speed Limit - From/To Speed Limit is the posted or legal speed limit in each travel direction on a road. Speed Limit may be used to estimate link traversal times, to prioritise link selection during route calculation, to calculate timing of the route guidance, and for display purposes.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all TO_REF_SPEED_LIMIT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SPEED_LIMIT_SOURCE</attrlabl><attrdef>Speed Limit Source - Defines the source used for the From and To Ref Speed Limit information. Speed Limit Source provides information to speed limit recognition applications about the generalised source of the speed limits in the database, to allow the application to choose between the speed limit from the database and the speed limit from the camera.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>POSTED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>DERIVED</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LOW_MOBILITY</attrlabl><attrdef>Low Mobility - Indicates if the driving condition on the link is considered low mobility. The Low Mobility attribute provides for display of links differently from other functional class 5 and low speed category roads. It further distinguishes functionality of functional class 5 roads similar to the Parking Lot Road and Four-wheel Drive attributes. This information can be used in route calculation to avoid specific links.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>DRIVING CONDITION IS LOW MOBILITY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>DRIVING CONDITION IS NOT LOW MOBILITY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>DRIVING CONDITION IS NOT KNOWN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PUBLIC_ACCESS</attrlabl><attrdef>Public Access - The Public Access attribute indicates whether or not the Link allows public access. Route Calculation: The Public Access attribute indicates if the road element can be used in route calculation to avoid specific navigable links. Route Guidance: The Public Access attribute can be used in route guidance for additional guidance instructions. Map Display: The Public Access attribute can be used in map display to differentiate navigable links.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>TIME_ZONE</attrlabl><attrdef>Time Zone - Time Zone indicates the GMT time zone in which the Link is located. Time Zone can be used to identify the time zone applicable to an administrative area.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all TIME_ZONE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LENGTH</attrlabl><attrdef>Length - Length gives the length of the Link in metres.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LENGTH values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>GRADE_CATEGORY</attrlabl><attrdef>Grade Category - Identifies a change in slope based on driver perception. Can be used to identify multiple levels of road that are present at a single place. 1 - Up, 2 - Level, 3 - Down, NULL - Not Collected.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all GRADE_CATEGORY values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LIMITED_ACCESS_ROAD</attrlabl><attrdef>Limited Access Road - Limited Access Road indicates separately digitised, high speed roads where traffic is controlled by ramps. The Limited Access Road attribute can be used for map display, avoidance of freeway/motorway, and route guidance timing.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>No</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ROAD_CLASS</attrlabl><attrdef>Road Class - Road Class identifies a road network based on governmental classification. Road Class can be used for map display. Additionally, Road Class can be used for route guidance, e.g., "Enter the express highway" or "Enter the urban expressway.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ROAD_CLASS values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape_Length</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape Length - ESRI automatically caluclated shape length, not to be used for actual linear calculations, e.g., square miles.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape_Length values</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>