<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 Point Addresses Mexico Points for: Mexico in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>Point address based geocoding reference layer.</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-117.12398</westbc><eastbc>-86.72832</eastbc><northbc>32.71768</northbc><southbc>14.67588</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>Mexico</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>The positional accuracy of a given street segment depends on the value of the Enhanced Geometry (ENH_GEOM) attribute. Links with Enhanced Geometry = Y conform to accuracy requirements of +/-5 metres for absolute position and +/- 1 metre for relative position. NOTE: With some linear SDC datasets, there can be 5 different representations of linear street geometry, including one base layer plus 4 increasingly generalized layers, to support rapid display at different zoom levels. The process of generalization removes points, and therefore geometric detail, from the dataset in order to reduce dataset size and improve display times. The suffix number at the end of the base layer name indicates how much generalization has been applied - the higher the number, the more generalization. For example, streets3 is more generalized than streets2. The horizontal positional accuracy described here does NOT apply to these generalized layers, but only to the non-generalized base layer, which will not have a suffix number as part of its name, e.g., streets. The minimum length of any street segment, independent of generalization, is 2 meters/7 feet.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><spdoinfo><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf><sdtsterm><sdtstype>Entity Point</sdtstype><ptvctcnt>11951424</ptvctcnt></sdtsterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><spref><horizsys><geograph><latres>0.00001</latres><longres>0.00001</longres><geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit></geograph><geodetic><horizdn>D_WGS_1984</horizdn><ellips>WGS_1984</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis><denflat>298.257224</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>PointAddress_Mexico</enttypl><enttypd>Point address based geocoding reference layer.</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape - ESRI geometry object.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>POINT_ADDRESS_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Point Address ID - The Point Address ID is a unique identifier for the Point Address.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all POINT_ADDRESS_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LINK_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Link ID - Unique identifier for the Link to which the Street Address relates. Link ID is used to identify each link in the database.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LINK_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>STREET_ADDRESS_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Address ID - Unique identifier for a named, addressed navigable link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all STREET_ADDRESS_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ADDRESS</attrlabl><attrdef>Address - The Address is the Address of the point address.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ADDRESS values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ADDRESS_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Address  Type - Address Type identifies the type of the house number range assigned to the link. The Address Type is used in conjunction with related address attributes, and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>B</edomv><edomvd>BASE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>C</edomv><edomvd>CITY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>D</edomv><edomvd>COUNTY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>O</edomv><edomvd>OLD</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LANGUAGE_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>Language Code - The language associated with the feature name. The Language Code, in conjunction with Prefix, Feature Name, Street Type, and Suffix, can be used in destination selection, route guidance, and map display.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BUILDING_NAME</attrlabl><attrdef>Building Name - Building Name is a Point Address attribute to publish the name of the building that identifies the Point Address. For certain countries the Building Name is an alternative to the address for identifying a Point Address, and required to define the Point Address. The Building Name attribute can be used for destination selection. The Building name combination provides an addressable entity.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all BUILDING_NAME values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SIDE</attrlabl><attrdef>Side - The Side of the link where the POI is located.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>L</edomv><edomvd>LEFT SIDE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>R</edomv><edomvd>RIGHT SIDE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ARRIVAL_LINK_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Arrival Link ID - Arrival Link is the link with the drive-to Link for the Point Address. The Arrival Link represents the link where one would like to guided to when selecting a specific Point Address. Note: There are a few cases where the Arrival Link is a pedestrian-only link. The Arrival Link is used for route calculation and route guidance, and represents the drive-to Link for the Point Address.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ARRIVAL_LINK_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ARRIVAL_SIDE</attrlabl><attrdef>Arrival Side - Arrival Side indicates on which side of the Arrival Link the Point Address is located.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>L</edomv><edomvd>LEFT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>NEITHER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>R</edomv><edomvd>RIGHT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_LAT</attrlabl><attrdef>Display Latitude - The Display Latitude is the latitude of the display position of the POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all DISPLAY_LAT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_LON</attrlabl><attrdef>Display Longitude - The Display Longitude is the longitude of the display position of the POI.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all DISPLAY_LON values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ENHANCED</attrlabl><attrdef>Enhanced - Enhanced is an attribute to identify if the Point Feature has been verified or has been automatically generated. The Enhanced attribute can be used to differentiate between Point Addresses that are verified, and Point Addresses that are automatically generated but do not necessarily represent a verified position.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>Y</edomv><edomvd>Yes</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ISO_COUNTRY_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>ISO Country Code - A three-letter country code as defined by the International Organization for Standardization. The ISO Country Code indicates in which country the feature is located. Different layers describe different features. ISO Country Code attribution is applied to Navigable Links, Administrative Hierarchies, and POIs in various layers.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>MEX</edomv><edomvd>MEXICO</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ST_NAME</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Name - Street Name is the Full Street Name of the Link. This is the preferred street name for the Link. Street Name can also be a Route Number, Exit Number, or Junction Name, if such a name is the preferred Street Name.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ST_NAME values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ST_NM_PREF</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Name Prefix - Street Name Prefix is a directional identifier that precedes the Street Name of a road. The Street Name Prefix is included in the full name for roads. The full name should be used for route guidance and destination selection instead of individual components Street Name Prefix, Street Type, Street Name, and Street Name Suffix. If the full name is used for display or destination input list the Street Name Prefix should not be displayed after the name or Street Type, this may allow the Street Name Prefix to be confused with the Street Name Suffix.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ST_NM_PREF values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ST_TYP_BEF</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Type Before - Street Type Before indicates if the Street Type is before or after the Base Name. Street Type Before can be used to determine the placement of the Street Type for usage in destination selection, map display and route guidance.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ST_TYP_BEF values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ST_NM_BASE</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Name  Base - Street Name Base is the Base Name of the Street Name.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ST_NM_BASE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ST_NM_SUFF</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Name Suffix - A Street Name Suffix is a directional identifier that follows, but is not included in, the Street Name of a road. The Street Name Suffix is included in the full name for roads. The full name should be used for route guidance and destination selection instead of individual components Street Name Prefix, Street Type, Street Name, and Street Name Suffix. If the full name is used for display or destination input list the Street Name Prefix should not be displayed after the name or Street Type, this may allow the Street Name Prefix to be confused with the Street Name Suffix.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ST_NM_SUFF values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ST_TYP_AFT</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Type After - Street Type After is the Street Type of the Street Name. It is only published when the Street Type appears after the Base Name. See 5.58.8 Street Type Before (Streets).</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ST_TYP_AFT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ST_TYP_ATT</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Type Attachment - Street Type Attached indicates whether the Street Type is attached or separated by a space from the Base Name. Street Type Attached can be used to determine the location of the Street Type for usage in destination selection, map display and route guidance.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ST_TYP_ATT values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ZIP</attrlabl><attrdef>ZIP - ZIP Code.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ZIP values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LATITUDE</attrlabl><attrdef>Latitude - Latitude.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LATITUDE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LONGITUDE</attrlabl><attrdef>Longitude - Longitude.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LONGITUDE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CITY</attrlabl><attrdef>CITY - City.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CITY values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>STATE</attrlabl><attrdef>STATE - State abbreviation for the state within which the applicable postal code falls.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all STATE values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>COUNTY</attrlabl><attrdef>County - USPS county name within which the applicable postal code falls.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all COUNTY values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>STATE_NAME</attrlabl><attrdef>State Name - State Name.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all STATE_NAME values</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>