<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 Street Geocoding Cuba Polylines for: Cuba in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>Street geocoding table, avaiable for each country or territory.</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-84.94075</westbc><eastbc>-74.16073</eastbc><northbc>23.19818</northbc><southbc>19.84378</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey><themekey>cuba</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>Cuba</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>The positional accuracy of a given street segment depends on the value of the Enhanced Geometry (ENH_GEOM) attribute. Links with Enhanced Geometry = Y conform to accuracy requirements of +/-5 metres for absolute position and +/- 1 metre for relative position. NOTE: With some linear SDC datasets, there can be 5 different representations of linear street geometry, including one base layer plus 4 increasingly generalized layers, to support rapid display at different zoom levels. The process of generalization removes points, and therefore geometric detail, from the dataset in order to reduce dataset size and improve display times. The suffix number at the end of the base layer name indicates how much generalization has been applied - the higher the number, the more generalization. For example, streets3 is more generalized than streets2. The horizontal positional accuracy described here does NOT apply to these generalized layers, but only to the non-generalized base layer, which will not have a suffix number as part of its name, e.g., streets. The minimum length of any street segment, independent of generalization, is 2 meters/7 feet.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><spdoinfo><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf><sdtsterm><sdtstype>String</sdtstype><ptvctcnt>88499</ptvctcnt></sdtsterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><spref><horizsys><geograph><latres>0.00001</latres><longres>0.00001</longres><geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit></geograph><geodetic><horizdn>D_WGS_1984</horizdn><ellips>WGS_1984</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis><denflat>298.257224</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>StreetGeocoding_Cuba</enttypl><enttypd>Street geocoding table, avaiable for each country or territory.</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape - ESRI geometry object.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Link_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Link ID - Unique identifier for the Link to which the Street Address relates. Link ID is used to identify each link in the database.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Link_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Seq_Num</attrlabl><attrdef>Sequence Number - Sequence Number defines the order of the components in the Aggregated Feature.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Seq_Num values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ISO_Country_Code</attrlabl><attrdef>ISO Country Code - A three-letter country code as defined by the International Organization for Standardization. The ISO Country Code indicates in which country the feature is located. Different layers describe different features. ISO Country Code attribution is applied to Navigable Links, Administrative Hierarchies, and POIs in various layers.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>CUB</edomv><edomvd>CUBA</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Street_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Name - The Street Name attribute is the full spelling of the street name including the Street Name Prefix, Street Name Suffix and Street Type.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Street_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Street_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Langcode - Is the Language Code for the Street Name.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Base_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Base Name - The Base Name part of the Street Name.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Base_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Street_Type_Before</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Type Before - Street Type Before indicates if the Street Type is before or after the Base Name. Street Type Before can be used to determine the placement of the Street Type for usage in destination selection, map display and route guidance.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Street_Type_Before values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Street_Type_After</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Type After - Street Type After is the Street Type of the Street Name. It is only published when the Street Type appears after the Base Name. See 5.58.8 Street Type Before (Streets).</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Street_Type_After values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Street_Type_Attached</attrlabl><attrdef>Street Type Attached - Street Type Attached indicates whether the Street Type is attached or separated by a space fromthe Base Name. Street Type Attached can be used to determine the location of the Street Type for usage in destination selection, map display and route guidance.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Street_Type_Attached values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Prefix</attrlabl><attrdef>Prefix - Prefix is a directional identifier that precedes the Feature Name of a road.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Suffix</attrlabl><attrdef>Suffix - Suffix is a directional identifier that follows, but is not included in, the Feature Name of a road.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>E</edomv><edomvd>Este</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>Norte</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NE</edomv><edomvd>Nord-Este</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>O</edomv><edomvd>Oeste</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>S</edomv><edomvd>Sur</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Name_Type</attrlabl><attrdef>Name Type - The Name Type indicates the type of name associated to the Zone. All Area Names (Base, Abbreviation, Exonyms, Synonyms and Shortened) can be used for destination selection and map display for languages supported by HERE.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>S</edomv><edomvd>Street Name</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Route_Type</attrlabl><attrdef>Route Type - The route type indicates that the road's name is actually a route number and in many countries is displayed in a shield symbol (i.e. Interstate and State routes in the U.S.). Name Route Type can be used for display and map publication to display the appropriate route shield when used in conjunction with the Direction on Sign.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Preferred_Street_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Preferred Street Name - Preferred Street Name is a flag that indicates if the Street Name is the preferred street name for the link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Preferred_Street_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Start_Address</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Start Address - This is the house number on the left side of the the reference end of the Link. The Left Start Address is used in conjunction with related address attributes and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_Start_Address values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_End_Address</attrlabl><attrdef>Left End Address - This is the house number on the left side of the non-reference end of the Link. The Left End Address is used in conjunction with related address attributes and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_End_Address values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Scheme</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Scheme - The numbering scheme for the addresses assigned to the left side of the link. The Left Address Scheme is used in conjunction with related address attributes and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Format</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Address Format - The format of the addresses on the left side of the link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Start_Address</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Start Address - This is the house number on the right side of the the reference end of the Link. The right Start Address is used in conjunction with related address attributes and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_Start_Address values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_End_Address</attrlabl><attrdef>Right End Address - This is the house number on the right side of the non-reference end of the Link. The right End Address is used in conjunction with related address attributes and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_End_Address values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Scheme</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Scheme - The numbering scheme for the addresses assigned to the right side of the link. The Right Address Scheme is used in conjunction with related address attributes and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Format</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Address Format - The format of the addresses on the right side of the link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Address_Type</attrlabl><attrdef>Address  Type - Address Type identifies the type of the house number range assigned to the link. The Address Type is used in conjunction with related address attributes, and the associated name for destination selection and geocoding.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Country_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Country Name - The Country Name is the name of the country.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Country_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Country_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Country LangCode - The Country Language Code is the MARC Language Code of the country.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Order1_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Order1 Name - The Left Order1 Name is the order1 name published on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_Order1_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Order1_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Order1 LangCode - The Left Order1 Language Code is the Language Code of the order1 name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Order2_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Order2 Name - The Left Order2 Name is the order2 name published on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_Order2_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Order2_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Order2 LangCode - The Left Order2 Language Code is the Language Code of the order2 name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Order8_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Order8 Name - The Left Order8 Name is the order8 name published on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_Order8_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Order8_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Order8 LangCode - The Left Order8 Language Code is the Language Code of the order8 name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Builtup_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Builtup Name - The Left Built-up Name is the built-up name published on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_Builtup_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Builtup_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Builtup LangCode - The Left Built-up Language Code is the Language Code of the built-up name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Order1_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Order1 Name - The Right Order1 Name is the order1 name published on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_Order1_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Order1_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Order1 LangCode - The Right Order1 Language Code is the Language Code of the order1 name on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Order2_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Order2 Name - The Right Order2 Name is the order2 name published on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_Order2_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Order2_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Order2 LangCode - The Right Order2 Language Code is the Language Code of the order2 name on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Order8_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Order8 Name - The Right Order8 Name is the order8 name published on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_Order8_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Order8_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Order8 LangCode - The Right Order8 Language Code is the Language Code of the order8 name on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Builtup_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Builtup Name - The Right Built-up Name is the built-up name published on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_Builtup_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Builtup_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Builtup LangCode - The Right Built-up Language Code is the Language Code of the built-up name on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Postal_Code</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Postal Code - The postal code for the left side of the link. A Postal Code represents the code generated by the government to facilitate mail delivery. While this feature can be used for destination  election this is usually not recommended, except in the case of refined address resolution. For example, when the same address exists twice within a city a postal code selection may narrow down which address is preferred.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_Postal_Code values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Postal_Code</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Postal Code - The postal code for the right side of the link. A Postal Code represents the code generated by the government to facilitate mail delivery. While this feature can be used for destination  election this is usually not recommended, except in the case of refined address resolution. For example, when the same address exists twice within a city a postal code selection may narrow down which address is preferred.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_Postal_Code values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Zone_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Zone Name - The Zone Name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Left_Zone_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Left_Zone_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Left Zone Name Language Code - The MARC Language Code applicable to the Zone Name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Zone_Name</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Zone Name - The Zone Name on the right side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Right_Zone_Name values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Right_Zone_LangCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Right Zone LangCode - The MARC Language Code applicable to the Zone Name on the left side of the Link.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape_Length</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape Length - ESRI automatically caluclated shape length, not to be used for actual linear calculations, e.g., square miles.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape_Length values</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>