<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 Admin Names Table for: Southern Caribbean in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>Table AdminNames stores all names for administrative areas of all levels. One administrative area can have multiple names. The Name Type indicates the type of name for the administrative area.</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-70.06405</westbc><eastbc>-59.4201</eastbc><northbc>18.61278</northbc><southbc>10.04279</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey><themekey>administrative levels</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>the Southern Caribbean</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>There is no positional accuracy directly associated with non-geometric tables.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>AdminNames</enttypl><enttypd>Table AdminNames stores all names for administrative areas of all levels. One administrative area can have multiple names. The Name Type indicates the type of name for the administrative area.</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ADMIN_PLACE_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Admin Place ID - The Admin Place ID is a unique identifier of the lowest administrative level in the hierarchy.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all ADMIN_PLACE_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NAME_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Name ID - The Name ID is a unique identifier for the Name associated to the Zone.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all NAME_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NAME_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Name Type - The Name Type indicates the type of name associated to the Zone. All Area Names (Base, Abbreviation, Exonyms, Synonyms and Shortened) can be used for destination selection and map display for languages supported by HERE.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>B</edomv><edomvd>BASE NAME</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>E</edomv><edomvd>EXONYM</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LANGUAGE_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>Language Code - The language associated with the feature name. The Language Code, in conjunction with Prefix, Feature Name, Street Type, and Suffix, can be used in destination selection, route guidance, and map display.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>ARA</edomv><edomvd>ARABIC</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>BAQ</edomv><edomvd>BASQUE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>BUL</edomv><edomvd>BULGARIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>CAT</edomv><edomvd>CATALAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>CHI</edomv><edomvd>CHINESE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>CHT</edomv><edomvd>TRADITIONAL CHINESE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>CZE</edomv><edomvd>CZECH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>DAN</edomv><edomvd>DANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>DUT</edomv><edomvd>DUTCH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>ENG</edomv><edomvd>ENGLISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>EST</edomv><edomvd>ESTONIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>FIN</edomv><edomvd>FINNISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>FRE</edomv><edomvd>FRENCH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>GER</edomv><edomvd>GERMAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>HEB</edomv><edomvd>HEBREW</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>HIN</edomv><edomvd>HINDI</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>HUN</edomv><edomvd>HUNGARIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>ICE</edomv><edomvd>ICELANDIC</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>IND</edomv><edomvd>BAHASA INDONESIA</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>ITA</edomv><edomvd>ITALIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>JPN</edomv><edomvd>JAPANESE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>KOR</edomv><edomvd>KOREAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>LAV</edomv><edomvd>LATVIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>LIT</edomv><edomvd>LITHUANIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>MAY</edomv><edomvd>MALAY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NOR</edomv><edomvd>NORWEGIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>POL</edomv><edomvd>POLISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>POR</edomv><edomvd>PORTUGUESE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>RUM</edomv><edomvd>ROMANIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>RUS</edomv><edomvd>RUSSIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SCR</edomv><edomvd>CROATIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SLO</edomv><edomvd>SLOVAK</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SPA</edomv><edomvd>SPANISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SRB</edomv><edomvd>SERBIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SWE</edomv><edomvd>SWEDISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>THA</edomv><edomvd>THAI</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>TUR</edomv><edomvd>TURKISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>UKR</edomv><edomvd>UKRAINIAN</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>VIE</edomv><edomvd>VIETNAMESE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>WEN</edomv><edomvd>WORLD ENGLISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NAME</attrlabl><attrdef>Name - The full description of the Name.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all NAME values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>PREFERRED</attrlabl><attrdef>Preferred - Preferred indicates if the Name is the Preferred Name for the Zone.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all PREFERRED values</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>