<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>HERE</origin><pubdate>20200701</pubdate><title>HERE 2020 Q3 Map Water Link Polylines for: Southern Caribbean in File Geodatabase Format</title><geoform>Vector digital data</geoform><onlink>https://company.here.com/here/</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>Layer MapWaterLink stores all linear water boundaries on a per-link basis. The preferred name for display is stored in the MapWaterLink Layer. Alternate names are obtained via the MapLinkNames table.</abstract><purpose>Road network navigation and routing, geocoding, location-based services, and base mapping applications.</purpose></descript><timeperd><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20200701</begdate><enddate>20200930</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo><current>publication date</current></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>2 times per year</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-62.86326</westbc><eastbc>-60.52053</eastbc><northbc>17.41104</northbc><southbc>10.06911</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>location</themekey></theme><theme><themekt>None</themekt><themekey>roadmap</themekey><themekey>navigation</themekey><themekey>routing</themekey><themekey>geocoding</themekey><themekey>HERE</themekey><themekey>linear water boundaries</themekey></theme><place><placekt>None</placekt><placekey>the Southern Caribbean</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>Access to this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</accconst><useconst>Use of this data is allowed only to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in HERE licensing terms and agreements.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac><datacred>HERE incorporates and enhances data from a number of local governments, utility companies, other public agencies, and commercial mapping agencies in building its final products.</datacred><native>ESRI ArcGIS versions 10.3 and higher.</native></idinfo><dataqual><attracc><attraccr>HERE advanced map-building capabilities, local field staff and a fleet of LIDAR equipped TRUE vehicles capture the world down to centimeter level precision to build a virtual 3D model of the real world. In addition, internal test applications are regularly run on attributes to assist in verification and correction.</attraccr></attracc><logic>HERE publishes Technical Notification Memorandums (TNM) for customers on a quarterly and weekly basis via HERE TNM Web Portal. These TNMs include information pertaining to product updates, format changes, new attributes, detailed attribute specifications and representations, and new country coverage announcements. If HERE plans to add, remove, or change an attribute or product Layer, an announcement is made to customers a minimum of 6 months in advance. This allows customers to prepare and make necessary modifications to their applications before a new attribute is released in the product.</logic><complete>HERE includes 4 levels of street map coverage: Prime, Complete, Network, and City-to-City. Prime is HERE's highest level of coverage.  This coverage level has the most detail and enables door-to-door routing functionality. Complete is a level of coverage, which is source dependent. It is the coverage level used for links that are not field verified and are flagged with the In-Process Data attribute = Y. Network coverage includes the main highway network and all the necessary attributes required to allow routing from city to city. Network links are coded with Detailed City Inclusion attribute = N and In-Process Data attribute = N. For Network links, the Full Geometry flag may be set to either yes or no depending on the presence or lack of surrounding In-Process Data Coverage. The City-to-City specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing Prime, Network, or In- Process areas. Examples include: major roads only in a country where there is no existing coverage, major roads to a city in a country where there is currently no other existing coverage, or major roads between existing DC/Prime, IT/Network, or In-Process areas. In many countries, HERE has used a commercial source to add local roads to the Inter-Town network. The inclusion of this geometry allows improved map display and guidance. This coverage level is called Full Coverage in the U.S. and Road Network Coverage in Europe. The Connector Specification enables HERE to maintain minimum coverage in areas prior to completing (full) Prime, Network/Inter Town (IT), or In-Process areas. For defining a hierarchical network used to determine a logical and efficient route for a traveler, each map street segment is tagged with a 5 level Functional Class (FC) attribute explained as follows. FC 1: Very long distance routes between major cities - The "highest level" network comprises the FC 1 arterials, which are primarily controlled access highways designed for very-long-distance travel linking major metropolitan areas and cities, FC 2: Primary routes between major and smaller cities and through metro areas, FC 3: Major routes between minor cities or towns, and through city districts, FC 4: Routes connecting minor towns or villages and collecting the local traffic in the city districts, and FC 5: Roads that are not efficient through routes - The "lowest level" and final category is FC 5, which comprises roads not considered to be arterials or transportation corridors.</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>The positional accuracy of a given street segment depends on the value of the Enhanced Geometry (ENH_GEOM) attribute. Links with Enhanced Geometry = Y conform to accuracy requirements of +/-5 metres for absolute position and +/- 1 metre for relative position. NOTE: With some linear SDC datasets, there can be 5 different representations of linear street geometry, including one base layer plus 4 increasingly generalized layers, to support rapid display at different zoom levels. The process of generalization removes points, and therefore geometric detail, from the dataset in order to reduce dataset size and improve display times. The suffix number at the end of the base layer name indicates how much generalization has been applied - the higher the number, the more generalization. For example, streets3 is more generalized than streets2. The horizontal positional accuracy described here does NOT apply to these generalized layers, but only to the non-generalized base layer, which will not have a suffix number as part of its name, e.g., streets. The minimum length of any street segment, independent of generalization, is 2 meters/7 feet.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>HERE File Geodatabase Plus is assembled from the following data sources: HERE North America FGDB, HERE Traffic Patterns, HERE Postal Code Boundaries, and HERE enhanced network routing and geocoding data entities and locators.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>Using proprietary tools and processes, HERE collects road geometry and approximately 400 road attributes. Proprietary software is used to add navigable information, addresses, and points of interest. TRUE vehicles and photos capture overhead signage to ensure that the data accurately reflects the real world.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE relies on local source data and input from map users to generate constant daily map updates, such as real time traffic, turn by turn directions, public transportation routes and information about local business and attractions.</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep><procstep><procdesc>HERE allows end users to update map content through the HERE Map Creator program, which provides online cartographic and data editing capabilities (https://mapcreator.here.com).</procdesc><procdate>Unknown</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><spdoinfo><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf><sdtsterm><sdtstype>String</sdtstype><ptvctcnt>3116</ptvctcnt></sdtsterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo><spref><horizsys><geograph><latres>0.00001</latres><longres>0.00001</longres><geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit></geograph><geodetic><horizdn>D_WGS_1984</horizdn><ellips>WGS_1984</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis><denflat>298.257224</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>MapWaterLink</enttypl><enttypd>Layer MapWaterLink stores all linear water boundaries on a per-link basis. The preferred name for display is stored in the MapWaterLink Layer. Alternate names are obtained via the MapLinkNames table.</enttypd><enttypds>HERE</enttypds></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Object ID - ESRI unique ID.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all OBJECTID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape - ESRI geometry object.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LINK_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Link ID - Unique identifier for the Link to which the Street Address relates. Link ID is used to identify each link in the database.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all LINK_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>FEATURE_TYPE</attrlabl><attrdef>Feature Type - Feature Type identifies the Grouped Structure or Grouped Complex with a predefined Feature Type.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>500412</edomv><edomvd>RIVER</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>CARTO_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Carto ID - Carto ID defines the unique Carto PVID to which the water Link is associated.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all CARTO_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_ID</attrlabl><attrdef>Display ID - The Display ID is a value which can be used for map display to render POIs in a logical manner.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all DISPLAY_ID values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>LANGUAGE_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>Language Code - The language associated with the feature name. The Language Code, in conjunction with Prefix, Feature Name, Street Type, and Suffix, can be used in destination selection, route guidance, and map display.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>ENG</edomv><edomvd>ENGLISH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>FRE</edomv><edomvd>FRENCH</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>NAME</attrlabl><attrdef>Name - The full description of the Name.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all NAME values</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DISPLAY_CLASS</attrlabl><attrdef>Display Class - Display Class is a classification of features that enables a meaningful display of these specific features.The classification is assigned according to the importance of the associated feature. Display Class information can be used to determine which features to display at different zoom levels. Display Class information can be used to prune out icons/landmarks of lower importance for memory-limited devices. Note: Display Class definitions for hydro-graphic features use different criteria for individual classes than Display Class for Landmarks/POIs.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>SIXTH CLASS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>SEVENTH CLASS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>EIGHTH CLASS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>COVERAGE_INDICATOR</attrlabl><attrdef>Coverage Indicator - Coverage Indicator is an attribute to a navigable or non-navigable link that indicates a product level that corresponds to the inclusion of database features. It also indicates verification and completeness for a particular feature in the database.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>E7</edomv><edomvd>ENTRY MAP</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>I2</edomv><edomvd>SEARCH AND DISPLAY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>I3</edomv><edomvd>DISPLAY ONLY</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N1</edomv><edomvd>COMPLETE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DETAILED_CITY</attrlabl><attrdef>Detailed City - This attribute specifies whether a link is part of a Detailed City coverage area. If Detailed City = N, then the inclusion level may be either Network, In-Process Data, or City-to-City. This attribute allows systems to adapt to different levels of attributing.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>N</edomv><edomvd>Not Detailed City Coverage Area</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>EXPANDED_INCLUSION</attrlabl><attrdef>Expanded Inclusion - Identifies cartographic features or links that meet the expanded inclusion criteria. This attribute makes all of the links or cartographic features meeting the expanded inclusion criteria easily identifiable. It allows for the option to not publish these links/ features if the inclusion causes size issues. Can be used to differentiate links included only for limited use from those published with limited use attribution. For example, when a portion of a hiking trail shares geometry with an unpaved road for use by autos, only those links dedicated for hiking are indicated for limited use only. Note: Features that exceed the standard size requirement do not receive Expanded Inclusion. However, features that are flagged as Expanded Inclusion at a lower Coverage Indicator level retain the Expanded Inclusion flag when the Coverage Indicator gets upgraded to a higher level where the Standard Inclusion size overlaps with that of the Expanded Inclusion. For example, if a lake feature flagged with Expanded Inclusion in Canada has a Coverage Indicator value of N4 and is upgraded to N0, it maintains the Expanded Inclusion flag regardless of meeting standard inclusion size for Coverage Indicator value = N0. If the Expanded Inclusion attribute does not apply to the link or cartographic feature, the attribute is not published. Prior to the Expanded Inclusion initiative, Bridges and Tunnels were only included in the database if they are at least 200 metres in length. Expanded Inclusion allows for Bridges and Tunnels between 5 and 200 metres to be included (if they are significant). These newly included Bridges and Tunnels will have the Expanded Inclusion attribute applied.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NULL</edomv><edomvd>No Value</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>ISO_COUNTRY_CODE</attrlabl><attrdef>ISO Country Code - A three-letter country code as defined by the International Organization for Standardization. The ISO Country Code indicates in which country the feature is located. Different layers describe different features. ISO Country Code attribution is applied to Navigable Links, Administrative Hierarchies, and POIs in various layers.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>GLP</edomv><edomvd>GUADELOUPE</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>GRD</edomv><edomvd>GRENADA</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>KNA</edomv><edomvd>SAINT KITTS AND NEVIS</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>LCA</edomv><edomvd>SAINT LUCIA</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>MSR</edomv><edomvd>MONTSERRAT</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>TTO</edomv><edomvd>TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>VCT</edomv><edomvd>SAINT VINCENT AND THE GRENADINES</edomvd><edomvds>HERE</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape_Length</attrlabl><attrdef>Shape Length - ESRI automatically caluclated shape length, not to be used for actual linear calculations, e.g., square miles.</attrdef><attrdefs>HERE</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>The set of all Shape_Length values</udom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><distinfo><distrib><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal><country>US</country></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>DataRequestNA@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib><resdesc>HERE product file, multi-zip file packages in ESRI File Geodatabase format.</resdesc><distliab>This data can only be distributed to HERE customers, as detailed specifically in our licensing terms and agreements.</distliab><stdorder><digform><digtinfo><formname>ESRI File Geodatabase</formname><formvern>10.3</formvern><transize>44839731200</transize></digtinfo><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>https://HERE.flexnetoperations.com. requiring username and password as issued to customer by HERE. Immediate, easy, and secure download access for data and documentation through HERE's B2B website is the data delivery method. HERE customers also receive email notification when new releases or updates become available for data and documentation.</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt></digform><fees>Contact Sales for most current pricing information.</fees><ordering>Call 312-894-7000</ordering></stdorder></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20200701</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>HERE Technical Customer Support</cntorg></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>Mailing and Physical</addrtype><address>425 W Randolph Street</address><city>Chicago</city><state>IL</state><postal>60606</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>312-894-7000</cntvoice><cntemail>tcs@here.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc></metainfo></metadata>